{
  "quiz" : {
    "level_one" : {
      "question_eight" : {
        "answer_a" : "39",
        "answer_b" : "19",
        "answer_c" : "20",
        "answer_d" : "29",
        "correct_answer" : "20",
        "question" : "If nucleon number of potassium is 39, number of neutrons will be?"
      },
      "question_five" : {
        "answer_a" : "2,8 and 7",
        "answer_b" : "2,8 and 18",
        "answer_c" : "2,8,8 and 1",
        "answer_d" : "2,8,8 and 3",
        "correct_answer" : "2,8,8 and 1",
        "question" : "If proton number is 19, electron configuration will be?"
      },
      "question_four" : {
        "answer_a" : "Ionic bond",
        "answer_b" : "Covalent bond",
        "answer_c" : "Co-ordinate bond",
        "answer_d" : "Dative bond",
        "correct_answer" : "Co-ordinate bond",
        "question" : "When a single atom provides both electrons which are needed for completion of covalent bond, lead to"
      },
      "question_nine" : {
        "answer_a" : "1",
        "answer_b" : "2",
        "answer_c" : "3",
        "answer_d" : "4",
        "correct_answer" : "2",
        "question" : "In Al2Cl6, number of electron pairs donated by each Chloride ion are?"
      },
      "question_one" : {
        "answer_a" : "Number of electrons",
        "answer_b" : "Number of nucleons",
        "answer_c" : "Atomic number of element",
        "answer_d" : "Number of positrons",
        "correct_answer" : "Number of nucleons",
        "question" : "In an atom, number of protons and neutrons are added to obtain?"
      },
      "question_seven" : {
        "answer_a" : "Ammonia",
        "answer_b" : "Ammonium ion",
        "answer_c" : "Urea",
        "answer_d" : "Nitrogen",
        "correct_answer" : "Ammonium ion",
        "question" : "Dative covalent bond is found in?"
      },
      "question_six" : {
        "answer_a" : "1",
        "answer_b" : "2",
        "answer_c" : "3",
        "answer_d" : "4",
        "correct_answer" : "2",
        "question" : "Number of bonding pairs of electrons in water H2O is?"
      },
      "question_ten" : {
        "answer_a" : "Nitrogen",
        "answer_b" : "Oxygen",
        "answer_c" : "Fluorine",
        "answer_d" : "Neon",
        "correct_answer" : "Neon",
        "question" : "First element in periodic table to have 8 valence electrons is?"
      },
      "question_three" : {
        "answer_a" : "carbon dioxide (gas)",
        "answer_b" : "water (gas)",
        "answer_c" : "oxygen (gas)",
        "answer_d" : "Both A and B",
        "correct_answer" : "Both A and B",
        "question" : "Burning of glucose produces heat and"
      },
      "question_two" : {
        "answer_a" : "Ionic bonds",
        "answer_b" : "Covalent bonds",
        "answer_c" : "Metallic bonding",
        "answer_d" : "Co-ordinate bonding",
        "correct_answer" : "Ionic bonds",
        "question" : "Complete transfer of one or more electrons from one atom to different atom forms?"
      }
    },
    "level_three" : {
      "question_eight" : {
        "answer_a" : "Combustion",
        "answer_b" : "Thermal decomposition",
        "answer_c" : "Neutralization",
        "answer_d" : "Respiration",
        "correct_answer" : "Neutralization",
        "question" : "If NaOH(aq) reacts with HCl(aq), reaction can be known as"
      },
      "question_five" : {
        "answer_a" : "It is endothermic",
        "answer_b" : "It is exothermic",
        "answer_c" : "It gives off more heat than coal gas",
        "answer_d" : "It requires very little oxygen to burn",
        "correct_answer" : "It gives off more heat than coal gas",
        "question" : "Methane (CH4) is better fuel than Coal gas because"
      },
      "question_four" : {
        "answer_a" : "Hydroxides",
        "answer_b" : "Water vapors",
        "answer_c" : "Dilute acids",
        "answer_d" : "Hydrogen gas",
        "correct_answer" : "Water vapors",
        "question" : "On burning, hydrogen is changed into"
      },
      "question_nine" : {
        "answer_a" : "Is an endothermic reaction",
        "answer_b" : "Acts as fuel in rockets etc.",
        "answer_c" : "Is fatal for plant habitats",
        "answer_d" : "Results in acid rains",
        "correct_answer" : "Acts as fuel in rockets etc.",
        "question" : "Burning of hydrogen"
      },
      "question_one" : {
        "answer_a" : "It is basically an endothermic reaction",
        "answer_b" : "It gives off a lot of heat",
        "answer_c" : "It produces carbon monoxide",
        "answer_d" : "It contains a lot of carbon",
        "correct_answer" : "It gives off a lot of heat",
        "question" : "Methane (CH4) is an excellent fuel because"
      },
      "question_seven" : {
        "answer_a" : "Copper oxide",
        "answer_b" : "Nitrogen oxide",
        "answer_c" : "Oxygen",
        "answer_d" : "All of the above",
        "correct_answer" : "All of the above",
        "question" : "Under thermal decomposition, copper nitrate gets converted into"
      },
      "question_six" : {
        "answer_a" : "Carbonates",
        "answer_b" : "Hydroxides",
        "answer_c" : "Sulphates",
        "answer_d" : "Nitrates",
        "correct_answer" : "Sulphates",
        "question" : "Thermal decomposition does not occur in"
      },
      "question_ten" : {
        "answer_a" : "Oxidation",
        "answer_b" : "Activation",
        "answer_c" : "Combustion",
        "answer_d" : "Reduction",
        "correct_answer" : "Combustion",
        "question" : "Chemical reaction with oxygen is called"
      },
      "question_three" : {
        "answer_a" : "Chemical properties",
        "answer_b" : "Physical properties",
        "answer_c" : "Number of neutrons",
        "answer_d" : "Mass numbers",
        "correct_answer" : "Chemical properties",
        "question" : "Isotopes have similar"
      },
      "question_two" : {
        "answer_a" : "Silicon",
        "answer_b" : "Chlorine",
        "answer_c" : "Argon",
        "answer_d" : "Potassium",
        "correct_answer" : "Argon",
        "question" : "First element in periodic table to have 8 valence electrons in third shell is?"
      }
    },
    "level_two" : {
      "question_eight" : {
        "answer_a" : "Combustion",
        "answer_b" : "Thermal decomposition",
        "answer_c" : "Neutralization",
        "answer_d" : "Respiration",
        "correct_answer" : "Thermal decomposition",
        "question" : "Conversion of Copper Hydroxide (Cu(OH)2) into Copper Oxide (CuO) and water (H2O) is an example of"
      },
      "question_five" : {
        "answer_a" : "Cu2NO3 + H2O",
        "answer_b" : "Cu(NO3)2 + H2O",
        "answer_c" : "Cu(NO3)2 + H2",
        "answer_d" : "Cu(NO2)4 + H2",
        "correct_answer" : "Cu(NO3)2 + H2O",
        "question" : "Products of reaction CuO + HNO3 â†’ are"
      },
      "question_four" : {
        "answer_a" : "Mg",
        "answer_b" : "Mn",
        "answer_c" : "Hg",
        "answer_d" : "M",
        "correct_answer" : "Mg",
        "question" : "Symbol of Magnesium is"
      },
      "question_nine" : {
        "answer_a" : "Same number of protons",
        "answer_b" : "Same number of electrons",
        "answer_c" : "Different number of neutrons",
        "answer_d" : "All of these",
        "correct_answer" : "All of these",
        "question" : "Elements and their isotopes have"
      },
      "question_one" : {
        "answer_a" : "1",
        "answer_b" : "2",
        "answer_c" : "3",
        "answer_d" : "4",
        "correct_answer" : "2",
        "question" : "In ammonium ion, electrons required between hydrogen ion and nitrogen ion are?"
      },
      "question_seven" : {
        "answer_a" : "Coal",
        "answer_b" : "Oil",
        "answer_c" : "Petrol",
        "answer_d" : "All of these",
        "correct_answer" : "All of these",
        "question" : "Non-renewable fossil fuels include"
      },
      "question_six" : {
        "answer_a" : "Carbon dioxide (gas)",
        "answer_b" : "Water (gas)",
        "answer_c" : "Hydrogen gas",
        "answer_d" : "Both A and B",
        "correct_answer" : "Both A and B",
        "question" : "Burning of methane (CH4) gives off heat and"
      },
      "question_ten" : {
        "answer_a" : "Cooling methane",
        "answer_b" : "Cooling natural gas",
        "answer_c" : "Cooling carbon dioxide",
        "answer_d" : "Cooling nitrous oxide",
        "correct_answer" : "Cooling natural gas",
        "question" : "LPG is obtained by"
      },
      "question_three" : {
        "answer_a" : "CO2",
        "answer_b" : "SO2",
        "answer_c" : "P2O5",
        "answer_d" : "PbO",
        "correct_answer" : "PbO",
        "question" : "Acidic oxide do not include?"
      },
      "question_two" : {
        "answer_a" : "Helium",
        "answer_b" : "Neon",
        "answer_c" : "Argon",
        "answer_d" : "Xeon",
        "correct_answer" : "Helium",
        "question" : "All are noble gases except"
      }
    },
    "scores" : -1
  }
}
